Guide to the Stanford University, Queer Student Resources, Records SC0252
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2008-206
  - SU Gay & Lesbian Community Scrapbook Materials, before 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Gay Students Union/Gay Peoples Union at Stanford Scrapbook Volume I, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gay Peoples Union at Stanford Scrapbook Volume IV (1 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gay Peoples Union at Stanford Scrapbook Volume IV (2 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gay Peoples Union at Stanford Scrapbook Volume IV (3 of 3), 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Notebook: Gay Peoples Union at Stanford Scrapbook Volume V (1981-83) (Box 2)
  - Notebook: Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford Scrapbook October 1983 – September 1984 (Box 2)
  - Notebook: Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford Scrapbook October 1984 – September 1985 (Box 2)
  - Notebook: Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford Scrapbook October 1985 – September 1986 (Box 2)
- Additional Records, 1972-2007; Accession ARCH-2010-126
  - "Gay Liberation" statue incident, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Publicity, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Publicity pre-2004/2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Publicity, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Publicity, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Publicity, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Publicity, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Publicity, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Publicity, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Publicity [undated] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Valentine cards (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Vector magazine [contains article about Stanford Gay People's Union], 1972 Nov (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photographs (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Out on the Farm, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - New Student Orientation, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - New Student Orientation, 2003
  - Publicity 2001-2002 and undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Publicity undated (pre-2004-2005) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Posters, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 3)
- Additional Records, 1993-2014; Accession ARCH-2016-013
  - "The Report of the Dean of Students' Working Group on Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Student Needs", 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Private Lives, Public Struggles..." by Gerard Koskovich, 1996-04-30 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - LGBT CRC Resource/Information Packet, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Creating Queer Space at Stanford (exhibit), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fire!, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "The Time is Now: Stanford Needs a Director!!...", undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Buzzed Release Forms, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1993-2008 (Box 2)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-024
  Physical and digital material transferred to Stanford University Archives from the Don Kelly Collection of Gay Literature at Cushing Library, Texas A & M.
  - GPU News (Box 1)
  - Various publications (digital scans)
- Additional Records, 2016; Accession ARCH-2017-239
  - Trans Inclusivity, 2016 Dec (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Coming Out, 2016 Dec (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Community Engagement & Diversity (Box 1, Folder 3)